iroot.com 2019-05-09

# iRoot Privacy Policy

###  iRoot Privacy Policy 

iRoot cares about your privacy. We've developed the Privacy Policy that explains how we collect, use, disclose, and store your information. This Privacy Policy governs your use of iRoot website at www.iroot.com and all associated sites linked to www.iroot.com. The terms “iRoot,” “We,” “Us,” and “Our” refers to iRoot. The terms "you," "your," and "user" refer to the user of our Service. Before using our software, please read our terms and conditions, also put eyes on our periodical changes of Privacy Policy.  

**How We Collect Your Information**

All of your information is from the messages the you left on our website. For example, you may be asked to provide your personal information like email address, phone model and others. Besides, we also have your information like where you click on our website and other Google Analytics tracking data. 

**What We Do with Your Information**

The personal information we gathered can help us improve our products, service, content and advertising. 

Also, we use your information to response to your requests, support of iRoot software and services. 

Otherwise, we use your information (like Google Analytics data) to improve our website content quality by data analysis and your search engine habit. 

**How We Use Cookies and Other Technology**

Cookies are placed on your computer's hard drive. You can choose to accept or refuse cookies while most web browsers automatically accept cookies. We can use cookies to analyses web traffic. Typically, we gater certain types of information such as your IP address, time and data of access, language use, the type of browser used and the page you request. The technologies help us understand user's behavior better. 

So if you want to close this part of information, feel free to set in your browsers. 

**Security of Your Information**

You have our words here: we will never sell, distribute or leave your personal information to anyone or any third parties unless we have your permissions. 

Also, we will preserve your private information well. 

**Children Part**

Our service in iRoot is not intended for person under the age of 13. We require that the user of iRoot software by individuals who are 13 years of age or older. iRoot.com does not allow to collect personal information from anyone under 13. 

**Contact Information**

We hope everyone learn the Privacy Policy before using iRoot apps. So if you have any problems on the terms and conditions, please contact us via support@iroot.com.
